A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2013.103: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2012; AC_2013_103; 26.2 Cubic Feet 20 standard record storage boxes, R4265-R4284; 20 standard record storage boxes, R4265-R4284
  - RES, AC_2013_103_7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2008 RES 305 - INSTITUTE FOR ALTERNATIVE FUTURES ? BC CONFERENCE: FORESIGHT FOR SMART GLOBALIZATION, 2008-2012 (Box R4273)
    - 2008 RES 306 - ORGANIZATION FOR ECONOMIC CO-OPERATION AND DEVELOPMENT - WORKSHOP ON INTERNATIONAL MIGRATION TO OECD COUNTRIES, 2008-2009 (Box R4274)
    - 2008 RES 306 - The Future of International Migration to OECD Countries - Published Material, 2008-2009; 2013:103:011 (Item 2013:103:011)
    - 2008 RES 308 - AMERICAS SOCIETY - IMMIGRATION AND INTEGRATION IN THE USA, 2007-2011 (Box R4274)
    - 2008 RES 308 - U.S. Business and Hispanic Integration: Expanding the Economic Contributions of Immigrants - Published Material, 2007-2011; 2013:103:012 (Item 2013:103:012)
  - Regional Nairobi (RN), AC_2013_103_8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RN 008 - (REGIONAL NAIROBI) - AFRICAN PROGRAM STRATEGY PAPERS, 2000-2004 (Box R4274)
    - 2000 RN 029 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - STRENGTHEN RESEARCH ON HIGHER EDUCATION IN AFRICA, 2000-2004 (Box R4274)
  - Special Program (SP), AC_2013_103_9; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2001 SP 114 - (SPECIAL PROGRAMS) - INDICATORS FOR EVALUATING PROGRESS OF COMMUNICATION FOR SOCIAL CHANGE PROCESS, 2001-2003 (Box R4274)
    - 2001 SP 203 - CHARITIES AID FOUNDATION (ENGLAND) - VENTURE PHILANTHROPY IN INDIA, 2001-2005 (Box R4275)
    - 2001 SP 203 - Mapping for Diaspora Investment in the Social Development Sector in India - Published Material, 2001-2005; 2013:103:014 (Item 2013:103:014)
    - 2001 SP 205 - LONDON SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS AND POLITICAL SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - STUDY ON GLOBAL GOVERNANCE, 2001-2004 (Box R4275)
    - 2001 SP 205 - Government and Opposition - Published Material, 2001-2004; 2013:103:028 (Item 2013:103:28)
    - 2001 SP 211 - ASIA SOCIETY - INDEPENDENT TASK FORCE ON INDIA AND SOUTH ASIA, 2001-2005 (Box R4275)
    - 2001 SP 212 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - ROLE OF U.N. IN REACHING MILLENIUM SUMMIT POVERTY REDUCTION GOALS, 2000-2007 (Box R4275)
    - 2001 SP 215 - SOLAR DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION - SOLAR DEVELOPMENT GROUP (1 and 1 SUPP.), 2001-2006 (Box R4275)
  - SOL, AC_2013_103_11; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2007 SOL 301 - INTERNATIONAL FERTILIZER DEVELOPMENT CENTER - IMPLEMENTATION OF THE ABUJA DECLARATION, 2007-2008 (Box R4274)
    - 2007 SOL 302 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - SYMPOSIUM ON INNOVATIONS AS KEY TO GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA, 2007-2008 (Box R4274)
  - EVA, AC_2013_103_12; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 EVA 301 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE ? BC CONFERENCE: PRIORITIES AND METRICS FOR A STEP-CHANGE IN ADAPTATION ACTION, 2008-2009 (Box R4274)
    - 2008 EVA 303 - OMG CENTER FOR COLLABORATIVE LEARNING - EVALUATION ROUNDTABLE, 2008-2010 (Box R4274)
    - 2008 EVA 304 - GLOBAL ACTION NETWORK - PROJECTS TO STRENGTHEN FIELD OF IMPACT EVALUATION, 2008-2012 (Box R4274)
- AC.2013.104: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1981-2013; AC_2013_104; 18.34 Cubic Feet 14 standard record storage boxes, R4291-R4304; 14 standard record storage boxes, R4291-R4304
  - Food Security (FS), AC_2013_104_1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - 2006 FS 019 - INTERNATIONAL FERTILIZER DEVELOPMENT CENTER - AFRICA FERTILIZER SUMMIT, 2005-2007 (Box R4291)
    - 2006 FS 019 - An African Green Revolution: Prepared for the Africa Fertilizer Summit - Digital, 2005-2007; 2013:104:012 (Item 2013:104:012)
    - 2006 FS 019 - Africa Fertilizer Summit Highlights June 2006 - Digital, 2005-2007; 2013:104:011 (Item 2013:104:011)
    - 2006 FS 019 - Africa Fertilizer Summit Proceedings - Published and Digital Material, 2005-2007; 2013:104:020, 2013:104:021 (Item 2013:104:020, 2013:104:021)
    - 2006 FS 020 - (FOOD SECURITY) - EXTERNAL ASSESSMENT OF RF-FUNDED CROP IMPROVEMENT TRAINING PROGRAMS IN AFRICA (Box R4291)
    - 2006 FS 021 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY - AFRICAN MAIZE RESISTANCE TO MAIZE STREAK VIRUS, 2006-2009 (Box R4291)
    - 2006 FS 022 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANISATION (UGANDA) - IMPROVEMENT OF EAST AFRICAN HIGHLAND BANANA, 2002-2009 (Box R4291)
    - 2006 FS 023 - TANZANIA - MINISTRY OF AGRICULTURE, FOOD AND COOPERATIVES - BREED FOR RESISTANCE TO RICE YELLOW MOTTLE VIRUS, 2006-2013 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 024 - (FOOD SECURITY) - FEASIBILITY STUDY FOR AN INVESTMENT FUND SERVING AGRIBUSINESS COMPANIES IN SOUTHERN AFRICA (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 025 - NORTH CAROLINA STATE UNIVERSITY - AFRICAN MAIZE RESISTANCE TO MAIZE STREAK VIRUS, 2006-2010 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 026 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - IMPROVED CASSAVA FOR COASTAL LOWLANDS, 2001-2008 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 028 - UNIVERSITY OF OTTAWA (CANADA) - SYNTHESIS OF INSECT RESISTANCE GENES FOR AFRICAN CROP IMPROVEMENT, 2006-2010 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 029 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANISATION (UGANDA) - CASSAVA IMPROVEMENT, 2002-2009 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 030 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRONOMIC RESEARCH (MOZAMBIQUE) - CASSAVA BROWN STREAK VIRUS, 2001-2012 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 031 - KICKSTART-INTERNATIONAL INC. - PROMOTE SALE OF MICRO-IRRIGATION TECHNOLOGIES WITH SEED AND FERTILIZER IN WESTERN KENYA, 2006-2008 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 032 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - GENETIC IMPROVEMENT OF DROUGHT TOLERANT RICE, 2002-2012 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 033 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - GENETIC IMPROVEMENT OF BUSH AND CLIMBING BEANS, 2000-2008 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 034 - MARKET MATTERS - SEED MARKET DEVELOPMENT FOR PRO-POOR AFRICAN SEED COMPANIES, 2002-2012 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 035 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - COORDINATED ECO-SYSTEM BREEDING FOR MAIZE IMPROVEMENT, 1998-2009 (Box R4292)
    - 2006 FS 039 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRI-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - DIALOGUE ON CROP BIOTECHNOLOGY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2002-2008 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 040 - (FOOD SECURITY) - COMMUNICATIONS STRATEGY FOR THE AFRICA FERTILIZER SUMMIT, 2005-2006 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 041 - HARVEST BIOTECH FOUNDATION INTERNATIONAL (KENYA) - IMPROVING ACCESS TO BANANA PLANTLETS, 2003-2009 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 041 - RF Report and Financial Report (2008) - Digital, 2003-2009; 2013:104:013 (Item 2013:104:013)
    - 2006 FS 042 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - ANALYSIS OF AGRONOMIC TRAITS IN CASSAVA, 2002-2007 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 043 - (FOOD SECURITY) - INCREASE SMALLHOLDER FARMERS' PRODUCTION IN AFRICA, 2006-2007 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 044 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - SYMBIOTIC FUNGI AND TISSUE CULTURE BANANAS, 2003-2007 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 045 - TECHNOSERVE - IMPROVE ACCESS TO MARKETS FOR POOR FARMERS GROWING BANANAS IN KENYA, 2003-2009 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 046 - TANZANIA MINISTRY OF AGRICULTURE, FOOD AND COOPERATIVES - GENETIC TRANSFORMATION OF CASSAVA AND VIRAL RESISTANCE, 2006-2012 (Box R4293)
    - 2006 FS 047 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - SYMPOSIUM OF THE AFRICAN SCIENCE ACADEMY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 2006-2007 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 048 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - VIRUS-FREE CASSAVA AND BANANAS AFFORDABLE TO SMALL-SCALE FARMERS, 2006-2010 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 049 - UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA - EFFECTS OF ADOPTION OF BT WHITE MAIZE, 2003-2010 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 050 - CHICAGO COUNCIL ON GLOBAL AFFAIRS - BOOK ON GLOBAL HUNGER AND GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA, 2006-2009 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 051 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - PLANT AND ANIMAL GENOME XV MEETING, 2006-2008 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 052 - (FOOD SECURITY) - THIRD MEETING: IMPROVED CROP VARIETIES FOR AFRICA, 2006-2007 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 052 - Biotechnology, Breeding and Seed Systems for African Crops: Research and Product Development that Reaches Farmers March 2007, 2006-2007; 2013:104:003 (Roll 1)
    - 2006 FS 053 - (FOOD SECURITY) - MONITORING AND EVALUATING EFFORTS TO INTERSECT FS ACTIVITIES IN WESTERN KENYA, 2004-2007 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 054 - AT UGANDA LTD. - NETWORK OF RURAL AGRICULTURAL INPUT SUPPLIERS IN EASTERN UGANDA, 2003-2008 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 056 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANISATION (UGANDA) - PROMOTION AND DEVELOPMENT OF IMPROVED HIGH-YIELDING BEANS, 2003-2012 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 057 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - DEVELOPMENT AND DISSEMINATION OF SUPERIOR CASSAVA CULTIVARS, 2002-2011 (Box R4294)
    - 2006 FS 059 - AFRICAN AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY FOUNDATION (KENYA) - GENERAL SUPPORT (1 MINUTES and 2), 2003-2010 (Box R4297)
    - 2006 FS 060 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - EXPAND PRODUCTION AND COMMERCIALIZATION OF SOYBEANS IN EASTERN AFRICA, 2004-2009 (Box R4297)
    - 2006 FS 061 - INFORMATION TRAINING AND OUTREACH CENTRE FOR AFRICA (SOUTH AFRICA) - STRENGTHEN INFORMATION LITERACY IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2006-2009 (Box R4297)
    - 2006 FS 062 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - NETWORK OF RESEARCHERS WORKING TO IMPROVE CASSAVA BREEDING, 2003-2010 (Box R4297)
    - 2006 FS 063 - REGIONAL UNIVERSITIES FORUM FOR CAPACITY BUILDING IN AGRICULTURE (UGANDA) - M.SC. TRAINING IN AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 2004-2009 (Box R4297)
    - 2007 FS 001 - (FOOD SECURITY) - CONTRACT WITH DEBORAH DELMER, 2007-2008 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 002 - INTERNATIONAL POTATO CENTER (PERU) - WEEVIL RESISTANCE IN AFRICAN SWEETPOTATO, 2004-2010 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 003 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENTIFIC AND INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH ORGANISATION (AUSTRALIA) - GENETIC ENHANCEMENT OF COWPEA, 2001-2011 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 004 - AGRICULTURAL COLLEGE OF THE HUMID TROPICAL REGION (COSTA RICA) - FIFTH GLOBAL CONFERENCE OF THE GLOBAL CONSORTIUM OF HIGHER EDUCATION AND RESEARCH FOR AGRICULTURE (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 005 - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF PLANT BIOLOGISTS - INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM OF PLANT BIOLOGISTS, 2007-2009 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 006 - SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE CENTRE FOR RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA (KENYA) - PROTOTYPE CEREAL BANKING SYSTEM OF MAIZE FOR POOR FARMERS, 2002-2008 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 007 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANISATION (UGANDA) - TRANSGENIC BANANAS AND PARASITE RESISTANCE, 2007-2013 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 008 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - AFRICAN RESISTANT MAIZE AGAINST STRIGA, 2004-2012 (Box R4298)
    - 2007 FS 009 - CAMBIA (AUSTRALIA) - NEW MODEL FOR MANAGING INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY, 2007-2012 (Box R4299)
    - 2007 FS 010 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - SOIL ORGANIC MATTER RECAPITALIZATION IN AFRICA, 2004-2010 (Box R4299)
    - 2007 FS 011 - AFRICAN ECONOMIC RESEARCH CONSORTIUM (KENYA) - COLLABORATIVE MASTER OF SCIENCE PROGRAM IN AGRICULTURAL AND APPLIED ECONOMICS, 2005-2009 (Box R4299)
    - 2007 FS 012 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - GATEKEEPER EDITOR PROGRAM; AGRA PROJECTS, 2007-2008 (Box R4299)
    - 2007 FS 014 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - EVALUATION OF RF PROGRAM ON DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN RICE, 2006-2013 (Box R4299)
    - 2008 FS 001 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - CONFERENCE AND BOOK CELEBRATING 25 YEARS OF AFRICAN HIGHER EDUCATION, 2008-2010 (Box R4299)
    - 2008 FS 001 - Proceedings of the 7th Biennial ASA Scientific Conference - Published Material, 2008-2010; 2013:104:004 (Item 2013:104:004)
    - 2008 FS 002 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - IMPROVE TIMING AND FLOWERING TRAITS IN CASSAVA AND TROPICAL FRUITS, 2004-2012 (Box R4299)
  - Conditional Cash Transfer, AC_2013_104_2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 CCT 301 - MDRC - BC CONFERENCE: INTERNATIONAL CONDITIONAL CASH TRANSFER (Box R4295)
  - CIF, AC_2013_104_3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 CIF 302 - 3-LEGGED DOG - COOPERATIVE PROFESSIONAL RESOURCES PROGRAM, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 303 - ALARM WILL SOUND - TWO MUSICAL PERFORMANCE WORKS, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 304 - BRONX COUNCIL ON THE ARTS - "BX 1: INDIE ARTS" PROJECT, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 305 - BRONX OVERALL ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION - "THE BRONX: BECOMING A CREATIVE CITY", 2008-2012 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 306 - CHEZ BUSHWICK - NORTH BROOKLYN COALITION OF ART AND PERFORMANCE SPACES, 2008-2012 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 307 - CREATIVE TIME - CREATIVE TIME ARTISTS' SOCIAL IMMERSION INITIATIVE, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 308 - DOWNTOWN COMMUNITY TELEVISION CENTER - DOC HOUSE DIGITAL CINEMA THEATRE, 2008-2010 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 309 - FRACTURED ATLAS - PROJECT, "PLACE and DISPLACED...", 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 310 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - HARMONY ATRIUM DISCOUNT TICKET FACILITY, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 311 - MISNOMER DANCE THEATRE - "AUDIENCE ENGAMENT PLATFORM" PROJECT, 2008-2012 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 312 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - STUDIO SPACE DIRECTORY, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 313 - NEW YORK HISTORICAL SOCIETY - EXHIBITION, "NUEVA YORK", 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 314 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - CENTER FOR GAMING RESEARCH AND DESIGN, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 315 - PARK AVENUE ARMORY - CONTEMPORARY ARTS EXHIBITION PROGRAM, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 316 - PERFORMA, INC. - PERFORMA09 BIENNIAL FESTIVAL, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
    - 2008 CIF 317 - TIMES SQUARE DISTRICT MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATION - ART TIMES SQUARE PROJECT, 2008-2011 (Box R4295)
  - Climate Chance (CLI), AC_2013_104_4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2007 CLI 001 - (CLIMATE CHANGE) - ASIAN CITIES WORKSHOP (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 202 - STRATUS CONSULTING - ASIAN CITIES, AGRICULTURE, AND CLIMATE CHANGE, 2009 (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 203 - KENNEDY, JULIE - CLIMATE CHANGE EVALUATION PLAN, 2007-2010 (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 204 - MOURELLE, EVA QUINTANA - CLIMATE CHANGE EVALUATION PLAN (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 205 - NEW YORK CITY OFFICE OF EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT - DESIGN COMPETITION FOR POST-DISASTER HOUSING, 2007-2009 (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 206 - INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (ENGLAND) - ASIAN CLIMATE CHANGE RESILIENCE PROGRAM (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 301 - SEI OXFORD OFFICE (ENGLAND) - CLIMATE CHANGE AND AFRICAN AGRICULTURE, 2007-2008 (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 309 - CENTER FOR CLEAN AIR POLICY - URBAN LEADERS ADAPTATION INITIATIVE, 2007-2011 (Box R4296)
    - 2007 CLI 310 - ENERGY AND RESOURCE INSTITUTE (INDIA) - 2008 DELHI SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT SUMMIT, 2007-2008 (Box R4296)
    - 2008 CLI 303 - AFRICAN ECONOMIC RESEARCH CONSORTIUM (KENYA) - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT AND CLIMATE CHANGE IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA CONFERENCE, 2007-2009 (Box R4296)
    - 2008 CLI 303 - The African Economic Research Consortium - Published Material, 2007-2009; 2013:104:017 (Item 2013:104:017)
    - 2008 CLI 303 - 20 Years of Capacity Building in Africa: An AERC Documentary - Digital, 2007-2009; 2013:104:018 (Item 2013:104:018)
    - 2008 CLI 303 - AERC 20th Anniversary Conference Natural Resource Management and Climate Change in Africa - Digital, 2007-2009; 2013:104:019 (Item 2013:104:019)
    - 2008 CLI 305 - UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN (DENMARK) - DIGITAL VEGETATION MAP, 2007-2012 (Box R4296)
    - 2008 CLI 308 - WORLD AGROFORESTRY CENTRE (KENYA) - WATER RESOURCES MANAGEMENT IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2007-2011 (Box R4296)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC_2013_104_5; 6.57 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 93022 #226; SI 9703; AH 9702 - RF 93022 #226 - UNIVERSITY OF CONNECTICUT - CHINA BRIDGES INTERNATIONAL FELLOWSHIPS (STORRS), 1997-2004 (Box R4300)
    - RF 93022 #228 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PUNJAB (PAKISTAN) - BT TOXIN GENES IN RICE, 1992-2004 (Box R4300)
    - RF 93022 #231 - MAHARAJA SAYAJIRAO UNIVERSITY OF BARODA (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR BHARAT B. CHATTOO, 2008-2009 (Box R4300)
    - RF 93022 #233 - ICAR RESEARCH COMPLEX FOR NEH REGION (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR HARI S. GUPTA, 1999-2007 (Box R4300)
    - RF 93022 #236 - PEKING UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR YI LI, 1999-2005 (Box R4300)
    - RF 93022 #239 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR GABRIEL O. ROMERO, 1999-2005 (Box R4300)
    - RF 94059 - YALE UNIVERSITY - WOMEN, FAMILIES AND TECHNOLOGY IN LOW-INCOME COUNTRIES (2 and 1 SUPPL.), 1986-2008 (Box R4300, Box R4301)
    - RF 96011 #116 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - UNIFIED THEORY OF FERTILITY DECLINE, 1997-2004 (Box R4301)
    - RF 96048 #62 - ASHISH GRAM RACHNA TRUST - REPRODUCTIVE AND CHILD HEALTH PROGRAM IN PUNE CITY, 1998-2005 (Box R4301)
    - RF 96048 #62 - B2 - Female Empowerment for R4 - Life Skill - Digital, 1998-2005; 2013:104:014 (Item 2013:104:014)
    - RF 96048 #62 - Impact of Nutritution Education - Digital, 1998-2005; 2013:104:015 (Item 2013:104:015)
    - RF 97001 #518 - G.B. PANT UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE AND TECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR JATINDER KUMAR, 1996-2004 (Box R4301)
    - RF 97001 #588 - LAHIRI MAJUMDER, A. N. - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES, 1995-2004 (Box R4301)
    - RF 97009 #9 - BAIF DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION (INDIA) - PRODUCTION SYSTEMS FOR JATROPHA CURCAS, 1998-2004 (Box R4301)
    - RF 97009 #9 - Jatropha and Other Perennial Oilseed Species - Published Material, 1998-2004; 2013:104:016 (Item 2013:104:016)
    - RF 97034 #854 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - ADIA: INTEGRATION INTO USHEPIA, 2000-2006 (Box R4301)
    - RF 97045 #85 - ANUSANDHAN TRUST (INDIA) - NATIONAL ABORTION ASSESSMENT STUDY (2 and 1 SUPPL.), 2000-2005 (Box R4301, Box R4302)
    - RF 97045 #86 - ZIMBABWE NATIONAL FAMILY PLANNING COUNCIL - HEALTH SERVICES FOR YOUNG PEOPLE, 1993-2006 (Box R4302)
    - RF 97045 #92 - POPULATION COUNCIL - FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES IN VIETNAM (4 FOLDERS), 1992-2005 (Box R4302, Box R4303)
    - RF 97045 #95 - SOCIETY FOR EDUCATION, ACTION AND RESEARCH IN COMMUNITY HEALTH (INDIA) - RESEARCH PAPERS ON REPRODUCTIVE AND CHILD HEALTH, AND CAPACITY-BUILDING, 1999-2005 (Box R4303)
    - RF 97047 #152 - INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (ENGLAND) - BOOK ON GENDER AND PRIMARY SCHOOLING IN AFRICA, 1999-2004 (Box R4303)
    - RF 97052 #593 - CENTER FOR THE INVESTIGATION OF CENTRAL AMERICAN REGIONS (GUATEMALA) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (2 FOLDERS), 1997-2004 (Box R4303)
    - RF 98001 #695 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - SALT AND DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN TRANSGENIC RICE, 1998-2004 (Box R4304)
    - RF 98001 #700 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR M. MAHESWARAN, 1998-2008 (Box R4304)
  - Separated Materials, 2013:104:001-2013:104:010
- AC.2013.105: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1981-2009; AC_2013_105; 26.2 Cubic Feet 20 standard record storage boxes, R4305-R4324; 21 standard record storage boxes, R4304-R4324
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC_2013_105_1; 20.96 Cubic Feet 16 record storage boxes
    - RF 98002 - (INTERNATIONAL CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY NETWORK) (INCLEN) (FORMERLY 197) (1 MINUTES and 10 and 2 SUPPL. and 2 Boxes), 1981-2004 (Box R4304, Box R4305, Box R4306, Box R4307, Box R4308)
    - RF 98002 - INCLEN - International Clinic Epidemiological Network - Digital, 1981-2004; 2013:105:001 (Item 2013:105:001)
    - RF 98002 - 1989 - Still Images, 1981-2004; 2013:105:002 (Box SF5)
    - RF 98002 - (INTERNATIONAL CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY NETWORK) (INCLEN) (FORMERLY 197) (1 MINUTES and10 and 2 SUPPL. and 2 Boxes), 1981-2004 (Box R4304, Box R4305, Box R4306, Box R4307, Box R4308)
    - RF 98002 - Word Perfect 5.0 - Goa.rpt, Goaz - Digital, 1981-2004; 2013:105:003 (Item 2013:105:003)
    - RF 98002 - (INTERNATIONAL CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY NETWORK) (INCLEN) (FORMERLY 197) (1 MINUTES and10 and 2 SUPPL. and 2 Boxes), 1981-2004 (Box R4304, Box R4305, Box R4306, Box R4307, Box R4308)
    - RF 97007 #29; RF 98011 #30 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - FOURTH INTERNATIONA MEETING OF CASSAVA BIOTECHNOLOGY NETWORK, 1997-1998 (Box R4304, Box R4305, Box R4306, Box R4307, Box R4308)
    - RF 98011 #32 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF SORGHUM FOR RESISTANCE TO FUNGAL DISEASE, 1997-2007 (Box R4308)
    - RF 98013 #162 - POPULATION COUNCIL - PUBLICATION OF SUPPLEMENT TO BELLAGIO CONFERENCE ON GLOBAL FERTILITY TRANSITION THEORY, 1998-2005 (Box R4308)
    - RF 98013 #162 - Health Transition Centre: Resistances to Behavioral Change to Reduce HIV/AIDS Infected in Predominantly Heterosexual Epidemics in Third World Countries - Published Material, 1998-2005; 2013:105:004 (Item 2013:105:004)
    - RF 98013 #168 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - ONSET OF FERTILITY DECLINE IN BANGLADESH, 1995-2005 (Box R4308)
    - RF 98020 #27 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - INTERNAL LABOR MARKET EVOLUTION AND LOW-SKILL WORKERS (LOWELL), 1998-2006 (Box R4308)
    - RF 98024 #95 - MEDICAL COLLEGE OF HAMPTON ROADS - PRIVATE/PUBLIC SECTOR COLLABORATION IN CONTRACEPTIVE RESEARCH (2and 1 SUPPL.), 1994-2006 (Box R4308)
    - RF 98036 #873 - UNIVERSITIY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - USHEPIA PROGRAMME PROJECT, 2000-2006 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98036 #887 - MWANGI, GITHIRI STEPHEN - ACA: COWPEA PEST RESISTANT GENES, 1999-2003 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98048 #6 - HASTINGS CENTER - PUBLIC PERSPECTIVES ON AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2006 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98048 #15 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER, 2000-2004 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98053 - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT FOR INTERNATIONAL PEACE - GLOBALIZATION AND EQUITY, 1998-2004 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98055 #601 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, "GATEWAY HUMANITIES FELLOWSHIPS PROGRAM", 1998-2008 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98055 #601 - 2-19-98 Tape 1 GCAC Gateway Fellows "Imaging Women of the Border: Elaborating an Art History of Chicana Mex Photography" - Audio/Visual, 1998-2008; 2013:105:005 (Item 2013:105:005)
    - RF 98055 #601 - 97 GCAC Gateway Fellows "Maria's Reflection: The Image of Chicanas and Mexican Women on the Boarder" 2/18/98 - Audio/Visual, 1998-2008; 2013:105:006 (Item 2013:105:006)
    - RF 98055 #602 - MARSHALL UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS (CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF ETHNICITY AND GENDER IN APPALACHIA) (2 FILES), 1997-2009 (Box R4309)
    - RF 98055 #602 - CDR - Appalachia Wired - Webs of Diversity - Disc I - Digital, 1997-2009; 2013:105:007 (Item 2013:105:007)
    - RF 98055 #602 - CDR - Appalachia Wired - Webs of Diversity - Disc II - Digital, 1997-2009; 2013:105:008 (Item 2013:105:008)
    - RF 98055 #602 - RF98055 #602 - RF 95003 #568 - CD-ROM, of find results of program use "view disc contents" function to review - Digital, 1997-2009; 2013:105:009 (Item 2013:105:009)
    - RF 98055 #604 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - RESIDENT FELLOWS: "COMMUNITY IN CONTENTION"(INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL STUDIES)(BERKELEY), 1998-2005 (Box R4310)
    - RF 98055 #605 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA - RESIDENT FELLOWS (CENTER FOR LATIN AMERICAN STUDIES), 1998-2004 (Box R4310)
    - RF 98055 #608 - VIRGINIA FOUNDATION FOR THE HUMANITIES AND PUBLIC POLICY - RESIDENT FELLOWS (INSTITUTE ON VIOLENCE, CULTURE AND SURVIVAL) (3 FOLDERS), 1994-2004 (Box R4310)
    - RF 98055 #613 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - COLLABORATIVE EXCHANGE OF SCHOLARS (CHAPEL HILL), 1999-2005 (Box R4310)
    - RF 98055 #615 - UNIVERSITY OF IOWA - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL AND COMPARATIVE STUDIES) (2 FILES), 1994-2005 (Box R4310)
    - RF 98055 #615 - UNIVERSITY OF IOWA - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL AND COMPARATIVE STUDIES) (2 FILES), 1994-2005 (Box R4311)